JOY HALLIDAY

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

DETAILS

PHONE

602-705-4094

EMAIL

tjoyhalliday@gmail.com

SKILLS

Microsoft Office

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Bootstrap

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

HTML

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

CSS

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Node.js

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

MySQL

• • 0 0 0

MongoDB

• • 0 0 0

Git

• • • • •

React

• • 0 0 0

JavaScript

• • • • • •

LINKS

Linkedin

<u>Github</u>

PROFILE

Early career full stack web developer with experience using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, MySQL. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Detail oriented and able to manage several projects at once. Experienced at working with a team of other developers in a virtual environment to create a cohesive application.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

The Music Index

Oct 2022

- · Web application built using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript using APIs
- · Group project completed virtually with four other bootcamp students

Gamesphere

Nov 2022

- · Web application built using bootstrap and MySQL using an MVC framework
- · Group project completed virtually with four other bootcamp students

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Loan Servicing Specialist, Wells Fargo

Chandler, AZ

Jul 2021 — Sep 2022

Mazda Universal Agent, Toyota Financial Services

Chandler, AZ

Jan 2021 — Jul 2021

Loan Servicing Representative, State Farm

Tempe, AZ

Feb 2019 — Jan 2021

EDUCATION

Full Stack Coding Certificate, University of Arizona

Sep 2022 — Dec 2022

Bachelor of Fine Arts, University of Arizona

Sep 2012 — Dec 2015